eq2flames.com 2010-12-22

# EQ2Flames.com Privacy Policy - EQ2Flames Forum

We are required to have a Privacy Policy linked from our main page to sign up with the major Internet advertising networks.

This policy doesn't change any pre-existing Site Rules or practices, it is merely posted to comply with advertiser policies.

**EQ2Flames Privacy Policy** **Effective Date: July 19, 2007**

EQ2Flames.com values the users of our website (the "Website"). Your privacy and trust are very important to us. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we collect when you use the Website. This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. By using the Website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [eq2flames@comcast.net](mailto:eq2flames@comcast.net).

**Does EQ2Flames.com Ever Make Changes to its Privacy Policy?**  
We may make changes to the Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting a notice on the Website, or sending a PM to your user inbox on this site. If you receive notification of a change in our Privacy Policy, you must review the new Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and procedures. You may not be able to receive notices from us if your cookies are not set to accept and/or are disabled.

**What Types of Information Does EQ2Flames.com Collect From Me?**

**Personal Information.** We only collect and retain the Personal Information that you provide to us, such as your email address or other information you may include in your user profile or provide at the time you register for an account here.

**Non-Personal Information.** We also collect non-personal information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous website you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your Internet protocol (IP) Address ("Non-Personal Information"). Non-Personal Information cannot be easily used to personally identify you.

**How and When Does EQ2Flames.com Collect This Information?**

**Providing Information to Us.** We collect Personal Information from you when you provide it to us. For example, when you register, we require your email address and IP number for verification purposes. Every time you post on this site, we record your IP number. If you choose to disclose or post other information on this site, including personally identifying information, that information will be retained and displayed as you posted it here. 

**Communications With Us.** If you communicate with us regarding the Website, we will collect any information that you provide to us in any such communication.

**Analytic and Reporting Technologies.** Like the operators of most websites, we use analytic and reporting technologies to record Non-Personal Information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software, operating system types, clickstream patterns, and the dates and times that the Website are accessed. We also contract with several online partners to help manage, monitor and optimize our Website to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising, communications and how visitors use the Website. To do this, we may use web beacons and cookies.

**How Does EQ2Flames.com Use My Information?**

**Personal Information.** We use Personal Information for our own internal purposes, and primarily to prevent individuals from signing up for more than one user account here. We may also use Personal Information to communicate with you when you report a post or initiate any other communication with the Administrators.

**Non-Personal Information.** We use Non-Personal Information to track the use of the Website and for other internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the Website and preventing individual users from registering multiple accounts.

**When Will EQ2Flames.com Disclose My Information to Third Parties?**  
**  
Disclosure to Successors.** We may disclose your Personal Information to any successor-in-interest of ours. While we have no plans for any transition at this time, and none have been previously discussed with any party, in the event EQ2Flames.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger or acquisition by or with another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by a notice on our Website of any such change in ownership or control of your Personal Information.

**Disclosure to Unaffiliated Third Parties.** We may disclose your Personal Information to prevent an emergency, to prevent harm to others, to respond to legal requirements such as a subpoeona or other court order, or to protect or enforce our rights and policies. 

**Disclosure to Third Party Service Providers and Online Partners.** We may contract with various third parties who help us provide, maintain and improve the Website. For example, we use a third party for advertising services and to process payments made to us, and may subcontract out production, fulfillment, analytics, reporting or other operations. We also contract with online partners to help manage, monitor and optimize our Website and to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising, communications and how visitors use the Website. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such third parties from disclosing your Personal Information, except for the purpose of providing the services in question. We cannot guarantee that such third parties will not disclose your Personal Information.

**Disclosure of Non-Personal Information.** We may disclose Non-Personal Information, in aggregate form, to potential strategic partners, advertisers, and others in a commercially reasonable manner and within the course and scope of our business. 

**What About Cookies and Web Beacons?**  
A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. Most websites use cookies. We use cookies to track your use of the Website and to allow you to login and begin use of the Website automatically when you visit the Website.

A web beacon is an often-transparent graphic image, usually no larger than a 1x1 pixel that is placed on a web page or in an e-mail that is used to monitor the behavior of the user visiting the Website or receiving the e-mail.

Cookies and web beacons used by EQ2Flames.com and our online partners are not linked to Personal Information. Some of our partners and contractors may use cookies or web beacons on our Website. We have no access to or control over these cookies and web beacons. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies and web beacons by EQ2Flames.com and our online partners only and does not cover the use of cookies or web beacons by any other third party or advertiser.

**Does EQ2Flames.com Protect My Personal Information?**

**Personal Information.** Whenever we obtain your Personal Information, we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, we are not insurers of the security of your Personal Information. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.

**Website Content.** The content that you store, post, or transmit on or through the Website, such as forum postings and images, may be accessed by other users, including people that you do not know. We are not responsible for the actions of others. Therefore, you should use care in communicating with other users and only disclose your Personal Information to other users that you know to be trustworthy. You should not assume that your content will be kept private.

**How Can I Review and Make Changes to My Personal Information?**

You can obtain a copy of and request that we correct errors in your Personal Information by emailing us at [eq2flames@comcast.net](mailto:eq2flames@comcast.net). For your protection, you will be required to provide proof of your identity to obtain a copy of your Personal Information. If your Personal Information changes or if you no longer want to use the Website, you may correct, update or deactivate your Personal Information and/or your account. If you would like to deactivate or terminate your account you can request that by emailing [eq2flames@comcast.net](mailto:eq2flames@comcast.net).

**Security** The security of your Personal Information is important to us. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Does This Privacy Policy Apply When I Access Third Party Websites?**

You may be able to access third party websites directly from the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply when you access third party websites. We cannot control how third parties may use Personal Information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third party website you visit before using it or disclosing your Personal Information to its provider.

**What About Children's Privacy?**  
**  
Under Thirteen.** EQ2Flames.com is intended for users ages 13 and older only. Accordingly, we will not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information from children that we know to be under the age of 13. In addition, we will delete any information in our database that we know originates from a child under the age of 13.

**Thirteen to Seventeen.** Users between the ages of 13 and 17 may only use EQ2Flames.com under their parents or legal guardian's supervision. If you are between the ages of 13 and 17, you, your parent, or your legal guardian may request that we deactivate any of your Personal Information in our database and/or opt-out from receiving communications from us. If you wish to do so, please contact us [eq2flames@comcast.net](mailto:eq2flames@comcast.net).

**Can I Opt-Out From Receiving Communications From EQ2Flames.com?**

We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your Personal Information used for certain purposes. We also offer you an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications through the User Profile screen. If you need assistance you may contact us at [eq2flames@comcast.net](mailto:eq2flames@comcast.net).

If we disclose your Personal Information to a third party in a manner that is not set forth in this Privacy Policy you will be notified so that you can make an informed choice about sharing your Personal Information with that third party.
